Can you survive 12 rounds for the one you love?
12 Rounds is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Renny Harlin.
When New Orleans Police Detective Danny Fisher stops a brilliant thief from getting away with
a multimillion-dollar heist, the thief's girlfriend is accidentally killed.
After escaping from prison, the criminal mastermind enacts his revenge, taunting Danny with 12 rounds of
near-impossible puzzles and tasks that he must somehow complete to save the life of the woman he loves.
Danny Fisher, played by John Cena.
Miles Jackson, played by Aidan Gillen.
Molly Porter, played by Ashley Scott.
George Aiken, played by Steve Harris.
Hank Carver, played by Brian J. White.
Ray Santiago, played by Gonzalo Menendez.
12 Rounds is a 2009 American action film directed by
Renny Harlin and produced by WWE Studios.
The cast is led by John Cena, alongside Aidan Gillen,
Steve Harris, Gonzalo Menendez, Brian J.
White, Ashley Scott, and Taylor Cole.
The film was released to theaters in the United States on March 27, 2009.
The film received generally negative reviews.
The film explores themes of police, cop, revenge, cat and mouse, family.
The tone is intense.